What the hell's going on with the sky in
America?
>> There's another chemtrail forming right
there.
>> In April of '25, I bought a homestead in
Costa Rica.
>> That does not look like a normal cloud.
>> I've been looking at the sky every day.
>> It looks like it's been parted down the
middle.
>> I have never once seen a single
chemtrail, but look at this stuff.
>> What is that?
>> chemtrails have we seen in Costa Rica?
>> Zero.
>> Quite literally zero.
>> What about the rain?
>> It's just it's nothing.
>> The rain is not sticky there like it is
here. But you can go two or three days
without taking a shower and your balls
ain't sticking to your legs.
>> I don't have balls.
>> Well, your
your your chest balls. Every time it
rains here in the states, you can smell
it, that ozone smell. You can smell it
drop as soon as it starts. But in Costa
Rica, there is no smell. And I was
thinking about that going, "Wow, water
is colorless, odorless, and tasteless.
So rain shouldn't have a smell, should
it?" No, it shouldn't. But dirty
polluted water passing through dirty
polluted air will have a smell. I think
if you look up, that might be the answer
why. I'm a simple man, not a sky
scientist, but I know that water is
colorless, odorless, and tasteless.
Something ain't right.
>> Yeah.